
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Salvatore Taibi</title>
  <subtitle></subtitle>
  <link href="" rel="self"/>
  <link href=""/>
  <updated>2022-02-05T22:41:57Z</updated>
  <id></id>
  <author>
    <name></name>
    <email></email>
  </author>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Looking Back, Thinking Ahead</title>
    <link href="/posts/first-post/"/>
    <updated>2022-01-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>/posts/first-post/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Where to begin? Times, they are a changin&#39;.
It&#39;s easy to take for granted all of the technology available at our fingertips today, therefore I find it useful to occasionally stop and think back to a different time. A time before all of this. A time when messages were sent in envelopes, a stamp neatly affixed in the upper right corner, senders and recipients both eager with anticipation. A walk to retrieve one&#39;s mail from a PO Box in the Rutgers&#39; Post Office (does it still exist?), hoping grandma sent a few dollars hidden inside a meticulously folded letter telling you to treat yourself to a meal but full-well knowing it was going to be spent on beer. What does grandma do now? Venmo? Bitcoin? The remarkable thing is all of this wasn&#39;t so long ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In any case, enough looking back. Let&#39;s cast our eyes forward. This is exciting. I wish I had a nickle for every time I&#39;ve heard: &amp;quot;Digital Humanities... That&#39;s the future.&amp;quot; Nevertheless, there certainly is a lot of truth in those words. The modern American landscape is soaked with opportunity. Anyone can publish their words and images on the web. All the tools are available open-source. Kids are given tablets and laptops at school, wifi is broadcast through the air. It&#39;s all free. Barriers to entry are disappearing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m not sure what role DH will play in my own work--mostly because I have no real idea of where I&#39;m going--but I know it will be a factor. I&#39;m already thinking of the possibilities of writing papers about cinema where clips are embedded and the reader can easily &amp;quot;see&amp;quot; what the article is referring to without having to search for the movie. My son would love nothing more than if I started included memes in my work. Perhaps that is how the two of us will collaborate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting to figure some of this out. The future&#39;s bright.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Second Post with Image</title>
    <link href="/posts/second-post-with-image/"/>
    <updated>2022-01-25T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>/posts/second-post-with-image/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is the part of the post that will appear as the excerpt.
Duis varius mi vel convallis lacinia. Vestibulum ante ipsum primis in faucibus orci luctus et ultrices posuere cubilia curae; Ut imperdiet tincidunt blandit. Morbi non pharetra lorem. Curabitur ultrices imperdiet quam vitae pretium. Etiam condimentum porta sem, ultricies fermentum enim condimentum vel. Morbi in massa magna. Donec eu lacus sed nunc molestie dapibus. Sed elit elit, semper eget dolor faucibus, porta fermentum ante. Fusce dolor velit, faucibus ac vulputate sed, tincidunt gravida ipsum. Morbi quis est ligula. Integer mattis, mi a pellentesque facilisis, enim libero iaculis libero, non blandit erat magna eu nisl.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1638452933982-8fa05063259a?ixlib=rb-1.2.1&amp;amp;ixid=MnwxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;w=1770&amp;amp;q=80&quot; alt=&quot;An image of blurred lights!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aliquam vel diam ac risus tempor gravida. Suspendisse cursus condimentum neque, consequat lacinia ex hendrerit ut. Vestibulum eget nulla eget elit pulvinar eleifend. Vivamus et ultricies risus. Cras hendrerit urna nec orci egestas convallis. Praesent placerat sodales tellus, posuere tristique ligula vestibulum id. Praesent dignissim ex vitae felis congue congue. Mauris facilisis sapien pretium tincidunt consequat. Aliquam eget odio felis. Vestibulum volutpat accumsan eleifend. Nulla porttitor mauris eget risus elementum, quis scelerisque ligula tempor. Suspendisse mattis eros leo, ut luctus erat viverra eu. Praesent pulvinar ipsum nibh, at faucibus felis bibendum et. Quisque a purus ligula.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>